# MOSTAFA ALSHAMMARY

m.alsham627@gmail.com | (623) 363-5283 | Phoenix, AZ 85014 <u>LinkedIn</u> | <u>GitHub</u> | <u>Portfolio</u>

## **SUMMARY:**

Highly motivated and dependable Web Developer with a superb work ethic. Committed to expanding knowledge and maintaining up-to-date industry knowledge. Experienced in HTML5, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Node Js. Great background in customer service and fluent in Arabic.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS:**

Node.Js, JavaScript, JQuery, GIT, Github, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Media Queries, APIs, JSON, AJAX, the command line, computer science fundamentals.

# **APPLICATIONS BUILT:**

## **Weather Dashboard**

- An efficient weather forecaster that displays live weather statistics by city and tracks a search history.
- Bootstrap, Luxon, JQuery
- Built front end in JavaScript, displays live time data through Luxon connections.
- <u>Link to application</u>

#### **Automate**

- A VIN decoder that displays statistics of the vehicle of which vin is entered.
- Lead developer of group of four
- Bulma, API, AJAX, JQuery, FontAwesome.
- Link to application

# **EXPERIENCE:**

# Rideshare driver, Self Employed

September 2018-Current

- Transportation of customers from and to their requested destination safely and timely
- Communicate with customers to ensure satisfaction and accurate navigation.
- Maintain a clean vehicle to ensure customer's maximum comfort.

# Transportation Brokerage Specialists

October 2016-December 2017

- Deliver Amazon Prime packages
- Sorting packages and inventory control
- Exceptional customer service

#### Spriggs INC.

April 2015-September 2016

- David Yurman store Security Guard
- Greeting Customers
- Record count of daily customers

#### **EDUCATION:**

# Trilogy, University of Arizona, Chandler, AZ

Coding BootCamp - Full Stack Web Development, in progress.

An intensive 12-week long boot camp dedicated to designing and building web applications. Skills learned consisted of HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Node Js.

# Arizona State University, Tempe, AZ

Ira A. Fulton Schools of Engineering - Mechanical Engineering

# Scottsdale Community College, Scottsdale, AZ

General Studies, University transfer credits.